[
    {
        "front": "かんじ",
        "back": "漢字 \nkanji",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんじ",
        "back": "漢字 \nkanji",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅうじ",
        "back": "習字 \ncalligraphy",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶん",
        "back": "文 \nsentence",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶんか",
        "back": "文化 \nculture",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶんがく",
        "back": "文学 \nliterature",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうもん",
        "back": "注文 \norder",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "＊もじ",
        "back": "＊文字 \ncharacter",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "おしえる",
        "back": "教える \nto teach",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうしつ",
        "back": "教室 \nclassroom",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうかい",
        "back": "教会 \nchurch",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうかしょ",
        "back": "教科書 \ntextbook",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "べんきょう",
        "back": "勉強 \nstudies",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ならう",
        "back": "習う \nto learn",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅうじ",
        "back": "習字 \ncalligraphy",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "れんしゅう",
        "back": "練習 \npractice",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふくしゅう",
        "back": "復習 \nrevision",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "よしゅう",
        "back": "予習 \npreparation for class",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅうかん",
        "back": "習慣 \ncustom",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいご",
        "back": "英語 \nenglish",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいこく",
        "back": "英国 \nbritain",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんこうしょ",
        "back": "参考書 \nreference book",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんがえる",
        "back": "考える \nto consider",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんこう",
        "back": "参考 \nto refer",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんきゅう",
        "back": "研究 \nresearch",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんきゅうしゃ",
        "back": "研究者 \nresearcher",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんきゅう",
        "back": "研究 \nresearch",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんきゅうしつ",
        "back": "研究室 \nresearch room",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    }
]